A Guide to the Office of the Vice President for Administration, University of Virginia Office Administrative Files, 1967-1974
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the Vice President for Administration, University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1967-1974
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/1/2.751
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1974 April 3.
Contents List
- Visitors--Miscellaneous (6 folders) 1966 Oct-1973 Jun (Box 1)
- Visitors--Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1973 Jul-1974 Jun (Box 2)
- U.Va. Demonstrations:
  - Completion of Course Requirements 1970 May (Box 2)
  - Communication with Parents of Students 1970 Jun (Box 2)
  - Crawford, Edwin--Correspondence to Staff 1970 Sep-1974 Oct (Box 2)
  - Drugs 1972 Apr-Aug (Box 2)
  - Flag Controversy 1971 Oct (Box 2)
  - Growth Demonstrations 1971 Oct-1972 Feb (Box 2)
  - Editorial Service 1972 Feb-1973 Jul (Box 2)
  - Fall Recess, 1970 1970 Apr-Sep (Box 2)
  - Information Services 1968 Jun-1975 Oct (Box 2)
  - Internal Communications 1971 Jan-1974 Oct (Box 3)
  - Judiciary Committee 1970 May-Jul (Box 3)
  - Kunstler & Rubin Appearances 1970 Apr-Jul (Box 3)
  - Law Enforcement 1968 May-1971 Jan (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (4 folders) 1968 Jun-1971 Feb (Box 3)
  - Newspaper Coverage 1970 Jul-Oct (Box 3)
  - Press Releases 1970 May 25 (Box 3)
  - Proposed Legislation 1970 May-Aug (Box 3)
  - Public Statements by University Administration 1970 May-Aug (Box 3)
  - Radio Coverage 1970 May (Box 3)
  - Referendum 1970 May (Box 3)
  - Student Council 1968 May-1969 Oct (Box 3)
  - Student Demands 1970 May (Box 3)
  - Student Hand-outs and posters n.d. (Box 3)
  - Office of Development 1971 May-1974 Jul (Box 4)
  - Office of Public Affairs, Miscellaneous 1970 Jun-1974 Aug 28 (Box 4)
  - Pavilion V 1968 Mar-1971 Aug (Box 4)
  - Office of Public Affairs (move to Monroe Hill) 1970 Jan-1974 Jan 1 (Box 4)
  - Office of Public Affairs (staff meeting) 1972 Mar (Box 4)
  - Paul Saunier 1967 Jun-1972 Nov 2 (Box 4)
  - Student Behavior 1973 Jan 8-Apr (Box 4)
  - Summary of Events 1970 May-Aug (Box 4)
  - Support of the University 1970 Jan-Aug (Box 4)
  - University Tuesday 1971 Oct (Box 4)
  - "Vietnam 1969 Moratorium" 1969 Oct (Box 4)
  - Widespread Campus Unrest 1970 Apr-1971 May (Box 4)